Things can't always be this way.
Especially now, Caloy!
I can already imagine it.
Her friends would invite me out.
"Hey, Abi! Let's have a drink."
Everything you said will happen.
Well? Is it okay now?
What is this?
"5:00 p.m."?
"At Le Jardin Hotel?"
Why were you talking with Val?
[YANI GRUNTS]
I was asking her
to help me propose to you.
- Bye! Take care!
- [PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Sweetie?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
A sorry letter?
For Billy?
Oh, it's a song.
[PEN THUDS]
Are you still affected by what happened?
Yeah.
This is my way of, like…
Expressing your guilt.
Something like that.
What about the promise you made to me?
You said you'd compose a song for me.
Um… did you forget something?
Ah…
[CHUCKLES]
I was just at the diner down the street.
It was too noisy here. I needed to think.
Think about…?
Here.
[VALERIE] Hi, Valerieverse fam.
This is me speaking up about
my ex's altercation incident.
As most of you guys know,
Jordan is a gentle soul.
But you also know
how protective he can be.
He will never hurt anyone unprovoked.
So this is me asking everyone
to stay respectful,
avoid spreading fake news,
and let the proper process unfold.
I have millions of followers
across all social media platforms.
I can ask them to repost it.
Val… Wow. Thank you.
But… why are you doing this?
Because I still…
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I still am a part of LoveList.
And just like Billy,
I love…
I love the company too.
Well, I can't thank you enough.
I'm just doing my job as a consultant
and a content creator.
Well, you deserve a raise.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[GASPS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Oliver?
Oliver!
No.
Don't go with him.
Don't.
Let's go.
Don't go with him!
Oliver, no!
No!
Oliver!
Come on.
[GASPS, BREATHING SHAKILY]
- [MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SIGHS]
[MUMBLES INAUDIBLY]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Oliver?
[MAN ON VIDEO] If you want
to throw killer punches,
you first need a firm stance.
Power starts from your feet,
not your fists.
- [GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [OLIVER HUFFING]
Good morning!
You're up early.
What are you doing?
I'm practicing boxing so I'm ready
when Biboy bullies me again.
[WHOOSHING]
Have you changed your patch?
Have you eaten yet?
Yes, Billy. I have everything
under control.
Okay.
Remember, just use boxing
to defend yourself.
Don't go starting fights, okay?
Wait, wait, wait.
I told you not to let it reach a point
where you have to defend
yourself, remember?
Avoid any fight.
Well, I'm good at dodging punches.
Look. I'll show you.
- Whoa.
- I'm good, right?
That's amazing!
Oliver. Let's go somewhere?
- Yeah. I'd like that.
- Okay.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JORDAN] Is it good, Grandpa?
It's a new addition to our menu.
Well, beef salpicao isn't usually
eaten for breakfast.
[CHUCKLES] But it's good.
- Thank you.
- Oh.
Don't tell your mom about this, okay?
She doesn't like me eating
fatty or greasy foods.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, Grandpa.
It'll be our secret.
[JUDE LAUGHING]
[JUDE] Okay.
[MUSIC BECOMES UNSETTLING]
Didn't I tell you to stay away
from my daughter and grandson?!
- [JORDAN] Grandpa!
- [THUD]
Grandpa, relax. Calm down.
It's okay. It's not him.
[JORDAN] Nurse, please
take him to his room.
I am so sorry.
Billy, did the caller contact you again?
I blocked the number, Auntie Pres.
Are you sure that will do?
What if he finds another way
to call you again?
Then I'll block it too.
If you want, you can give me the number.
I'll talk to that caller.
No need, Auntie Pres.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Let's go, Billy!
- Okay.
Auntie, you're not really coming with us?
I still have a lot to do here.
- You two have fun, okay?
- Okay.
- Ready? Kiss Auntie Pres goodbye.
- Let's go.
- Bye.
- Hmm.
- Enjoy, enjoy, enjoy.
- Bye, Auntie Pres.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
Mwah. Hmm?
Mm-hmm. Bye!
Bro, I'm sorry about what happened.
Please be patient with Grandpa.
I'm new here and I guess
Grandpa Jude didn't recognize me.
The thing is…
you and my dad are both bald.
They're not on good terms,
so seeing you must have triggered him.
Patients with Alzheimer's disease
tend to forget
their recent memories first.
But they find it hard to forget
deep emotional memories.
[EXHALES LOUDLY]
Perhaps you should avoid him for now.
- Okay, sir.
- Just to be safe.
Okay, sir.
- Thank you.
- Thank you too.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hey, dude.
I paid Grandpa a visit,
but I was about to leave.
Okay, game. I'll join you guys.
[GRUNTS]
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[PILLS RATTLING]
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy, can we go there, please?
- Okay, you go first.
- Thank you.
- We'll be right behind you. Go, go, go!
- Be careful!
[PHONE CHIMES]
You told her to do this, didn't you?
She volunteered.
I didn't tell her to.
Mm…
That means she still loves you.
Think about it.
That's one problem solved.
You're being defensive.
No.
You know, I believe
that Valerie is a good person.
I don't think she has
anything to do with Caloy.
Who I'm suing, by the way. Don't forget.
You know, to be honest,
I really got scared when I was in prison.
I kept thinking…
About what would happen to your grandpa.
How is he?
He's okay.
He was doing great
until he met the new staff member.
The guy looks like my dad.
He's also bald.
Grandpa got triggered.
So he acted out.
He attacked.
I'm sorry, dude.
Just try to understand your grandpa.
It's really hard
when you can't escape
the person who hurt you.
Are you okay?
Dude. What happened?
[CLEARS THROAT]
My father called last night.
What did he say?
I didn't listen to what he had to say.
I blocked his number immediately.
Auntie Pres said
that we should find out
why he was calling.
What for?
There's no point anyway, right?
It's your choice.
Billy, Bro Dude! Let's check out
the people boxing over there.
- Come on! Let's go!
- [BILLY] I think--
Oh, he said he wants to box.
Ask him to go with you.
- Go, go, go!
- Come on.
Okay. I'll teach you.
[OLIVER] Okay. Look!
Hurry!
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[TERE] Unbelievable!
Do you think this is your house, huh?
If that's so, at least keep it clean!
Look at all this mess!
You're treating this place like a bar!
- I've been patient with you!
- [ABI] Ms. Tere.
I'm sorry. One unit was broken,
so Caloy stayed overtime.
[TERE] Overtime?!
Abi, it's written on our contract
that this is a computer shop, not a motel.
It's called Click Station for a reason.
It's also written on our contract
that if you fail to pay rent
for two months, you have to leave.
It's been more than that,
and I'm still letting you stay.
And this is how you treat my place?!
- Seriously?!
- I know. I know, Ms. Tere!
I know!
So I'm going to ask you again
to give us more time.
Just a week.
A week?
One week.
Okay. If you fail to pay me,
I'm going to do a garage sale,
and I'll include all of your things.
- My gosh.
- Sure.
[LOUD THUD]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Look.
- Watch them.
- Amazing!
Wow! Someone's excited.
- Yes.
- Someone's excited!
The power comes from the legs.
Just like that.
Let's try it.
- Let's go.
- [BILLY] Go.
Show me your moves.
- Go, kiddo. Hit him hard.
- Follow what I do.
- Jab, jab.
- Go!
Straight.
Jab, jab, straight.
Nice.
- Okay. Nice moves.
- Yes.
Again.
- Jab, jab, straight.
- Pull your feet.
- Oliver, hit him harder!
- [OLIVER] Okay.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
CHIEF. LOAN CONCERN. CAN I CALL?
Dude. I just need to make a phone call.
- I'll get you some water too.
- [OLIVER] Okay, bye!
- [JORDAN] Sure. Okay.
- Be careful, okay? Careful!
Okay. Here's the next thing
that you should do.
Sorry.
I'm sorry. If only I had money,
I would've let you borrow it immediately.
It's fine. I expected that anyway.
[CALOY] I got some side hustles.
I'll see if I can earn some, okay?
I want to make it up to you.
[BOTTLES CLINK]
Hey.
You should take a break from working here.
I'm not going to get drunk anymore.
I won't drink here.
You really shouldn't be getting drunk.
It's dangerous when you get drunk.
Do you know what you called me
last night, huh?
- What?
- You called me Bea.
- B-Bea?
- Yes.
See? You can't remember
because you were wasted.
I've told you this before.
Even if it's just the two of us,
get used to calling me Abi!
- Abi! Abi! Abi! Abi! Abi!
- I'm sorry.
Abi, Abi, Abi.
- Get used to calling me Abi.
And we shouldn't be seen together.
Because your case
with Jordan isn't over yet.
- It'll be a big problem.
- [BOTTLES CLINKING]
Abi…
Are you firing me?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
No, Caloy. I'm not firing you.
What are you saying?
I need you, so why would I fire you?
All I'm saying is--
Stop smiling. I'm being serious here.
All I'm saying is stop coming
to the computer shop!
- That's all!
- [SUNGLASSES CLATTER]
What happened to your face?
My charge hit me. Tsk!
She's another problem.
We really are soulmates.
Soulmates, you say?
Want me to rip your soul out?
No, ma'am.
I'm being serious, okay?
Use your feet, okay?
Just like this. Ready?
Jab. Jab, straight.
- Like that.
- You're good, Bro Dude!
Where did you learn to box?
Grandpa Jude taught me.
He's a great fighter.
Your grandpa?
Why did your grandfather teach you
and not your father?
Haven't I told you?
My father left me.
It's actually been a while.
You didn't try to find him?
You don't know where he is?
- No.
- Why not?
I feel like things are
better off without him.
- Try to copy me.
- Okay.
Jab! Hook!
Good morning, chief!
Yes, chief.
The bank representative said
the title verification is still ongoing,
so they can't release the check yet.
- Thanks.
- Okay, got it.
I'll take care of this on Monday.
- Thank you, Blaire.
- Are you hungry?
Yes.
- Want some drinks?
- Two bottles of water, please.
- That'll be 25 each.
- Okay.
Here you go, dear.
Let me wipe off your sweat.
- [MAN 1] You should rest first.
- [GIRL 1] Mm-hmm.
[MAN 1] You're drenched in sweat!
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SELLER] Fifty pesos, miss.
- All right.
- Thank you.
[MAN 1] Play later. Let's eat lunch first.
[GIRL 1] Okay.
When your mom comes back.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC TURNS DRAMATIC]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Dear?
Dear, please hear me out.
I know I did you wrong,
but forgive me, dear!
Dear, let me explain--
That's not necessary.
We're fine now.
Just leave.
Dear, I'm begging you.
No, I am begging you.
Let this be the last time
we see each other.
[BILLY SNIFFLES, BREATHES SHAKILY]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAN 2] Dear!
- [GIRL 2] The fish is ready!
- [BOY 1] Let's eat!
- [BOY 2] Hurry up.
- [MAN 2] Okay, okay.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WOMAN] Wow!
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
- Hello?
- Hello? [SNIFFLES]
Oliver's still with you, right?
Uh, yes.
- Wait here.
- Okay.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Keep an eye on him. Please.
I'm on my way back.
Dude, what happened?
Jordan, my father is here.
[SNIFFLES] Let's go home. Please?
What?
Too bad you have to attend
an online meeting.
I didn't get to show you
what Bro Dude taught me.
[BILLY] I'm sorry. I'll make it up to you.
- Show me later.
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- Okay.
- Hey, are you okay?
[SNIFFLES]
[SIGHS SHAKILY]
You think he's still here?
[SNIFFLES]
Okay.
I'll drive you home.
I'll just come back for my bike later.
No. [SNIFFLES] I can drive.
- We'll go straight home.
- I know you're not okay.
[SNIFFLES]
Come on, dude.
Let me drive you home.
- [SHAKILY] Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay. [SNIFFLES]
- Let's go.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I wish we could visit
Papa's grave in America.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOORS CLOSING]
- Hey.
- Hi, Auntie Pres.
- Did you have fun?
- Yes! Let's do that again!
- Sure! Good night, kid.
- [OLIVER] Good night!
Dude.
You know you can talk to me.
Anytime, okay?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHISPERS] Thank you.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GATE CLINKS]
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING, THEN FADES]
Auntie Pres, I'll drop Oliver off
at school tomorrow, okay?
[BAG THUDS]
Jordan already told me what happened.
[BILLY SNIFFLES]
You want to talk about it?
I'm here for you.
[PRECIOUS SNIFFLES]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES]
Billy…
You know, when I first met you,
I was so impressed.
I thought, what an amazing kid you are.
I saw how hard you fought
for Oliver back then.
I realized just how deeply you loved him.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Even with all the kids
I've cared for at the center,
you made me realize
I wanted to be a mother.
So if it's okay with you,
let me be a mother to you just this once.
Is that all right?
Is that okay with you, Billy?
[PRECIOUS SNIFFLES]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why'd he even come back?
We were doing fine,
weren't we, Auntie Pres?
We were doing just fine.
Why's he showing up again?
He's ruining everything.
We were doing fine.
Mister, please buy something. Mister…
- Miss! Miss, please buy--
- Benilda?
- [PANICKED BREATHING]
- Benilda, wait! Hold on.
I won't let you take me away again!
I won't let you separate
my brother and me!
But it's for Oliver's own good.
For his own good?
When you're tearing us apart?
Family…
is never meant to be split up.
No one gets left behind.
But you're still not able
to take care of him yourself--
I can do it.
Yes, I can.
Just come with me, please.
Even if you take me again,
I'll run away with my brother.
No matter what you do,
I'll never leave his side.
I won't let anything happen to him.
I understand.
Believe me.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BOTH SNIFFLING, SOBBING SOFTLY]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you going to sue him?
If he won't stay away from me
and my brother.
You've got some nerve, huh?!
That's enough!
When are you meeting
Caloy again?
Next week. The subpoena
has already been issued.
See? You had him locked up.
He won't leave you alone.
He might dig up
more information about you.
I really do need extra work right now.
If an opening comes up
at LoveList, I'll let you know.
We have to be a hundred steps ahead.
You're exactly what I want.
The new canteen manager
stood up for me.
- I'll drop you off.
- Oh…
Do you really believe
what you said earlier?
Second chances
can be earned?
About your dad.
And you… do you think
you can forgive?